Get my kids off to school
Then I'm ready to get started
Sometimes there are some studies from home but often you sit out at the university
You meet some plug friends you sit and plug and maybe take a coffee it is mixed with lectures and seminars
But I put my studies
Between 8 and 5 in order to be able to get evenings and weekends free to devote myself to something else then
Yes when you start plugging it makes little difference with the economy
It may not be as much luxury holiday and spontaneous shopping anymore
But I think this is for a limited time
A difference is now also that when you have children and plugs
Should they get sick or you want to take vacation like that